[
  {
    "front": "Tutu",
    "back": "üê∑"
  },
  {
    "front": "Socks",
    "back": "Avocado"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sambuca and corn bread",
    "back": "The Blues Kitchen"
  },
  {
    "front": "Post rock",
    "back": "Explosions in the sky"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sang likes; tutu hates",
    "back": "Banana"
  },
  {
    "front": "Tutu likes; sang hates",
    "back": "Tomato"
  },
  {
    "front": "'It is simply there, when yesterday it was not.'",
    "back": "Night Circus"
  },
  {
    "front": "'Books are mirrors: you only see in them what you already have inside you.'",
    "back": "The Shadow of the Wind"
  },
  {
    "front": "World buffet",
    "back": "Za za bazaar"
  },
  {
    "front": "Conveyor belt",
    "back": "Kulu kulu"
  },
  {
    "front": "Better Call Stratford",
    "back": "Cinnabon"
  },
  {
    "front": "Peanut butter and chocolate",
    "back": "Reese's cups"
  },
  {
    "front": "Find strangers with common interests",
    "back": "Omegle"
  },
  {
    "front": "'If you live in each other's pockets long enough, you're related.'",
    "back": "The Pact"
  },
  {
    "front": "All is well",
    "back": "3 Idiots"
  },
  {
    "front": "'If you lose your purpose... it's like you're broken.'",
    "back": "Hugo"
  },
  {
    "front": "Pitted",
    "back": "Olive"
  },
  {
    "front": "Black butter",
    "back": "Jersey Island"
  },
  {
    "front": "VIP seats",
    "back": "Mousetrap"
  },
  {
    "front": "Indian",
    "back": "Rassasy"
  },
  {
    "front": "Punishment",
    "back": "Squats"
  },
  {
    "front": "Is the number on the back higher or lower than 22?",
    "back": "23"
  },
  {
    "front": "Is the number on the back higher or lower than 22?",
    "back": "2"
  }
]
